Railway Labor Executives' Association Records 5484
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series XII: Mergers, Acquisitions, and Abandonments, 1940-1976
  The records of the Penn Central merger are of particular interest. The Pennsylvania Railroad and the New York Central had been rivals, operating in the same areas of the country, since their inceptions. However, due to numerous financial considerations in the postwar era, the two companies began to discuss the possibility of a merger in the late 1950s. As a result of the freight traffic they handled as well as the passenger service both carriers operated into the major metropolitan centers of the East Coast, the ICC requirements for the merger, as well as the objections of labor organizations, rival carriers, and the concerns of the municipal governments, the merger took over a decade to be approved. The two companies merged in 1968, and as a requirement to the merger imposed by the ICC, they also absorbed the New Haven Railroad in 1969. The new carrier was called the Penn Central Transportation Company. In 1970, the Penn Central declared bankruptcy. This was the largest bankruptcy in U.S. history until the 2001 Enron bankruptcy. Extensive documentation of the merger proceedings are located in this series. The records of the bankruptcy may be found in Collections 5552 and 5728.
  Other major attempted mergers of note that are documented in this series are the ultimately unsuccessful attempt by the Chicago and North Western to acquire the Rock Island Railroad (Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railroad) and the proposed merger between the Union Pacific and Rock Island. This merger, which would have created a mega-system between Chicago and the West Coast, led to numerous objections being filed by other carriers. The proposed merger between the UP and the Rock Island resulted in 10 years of hearings in front of the ICC and voluminous filings by carriers, experts, labor organizations, and various state and local entities. It was also one of the most complicated cases ever heard before the ICC. The merger ultimately proved unsuccessful because at the end of the process, the Rock Island had lost too much value through discontinuance of lines and lack of repairs and maintenance on its rolling stock and facilities. In 1974, the ICC approved the merger but the UP withdrew its offer because the cost had become prohibitive. The Rock Island entered bankruptcy in 1975, and went out of business in 1980.
  Also of interest are the numerous applications by various railroads for the discontinuance of passenger services. The majority of railroad profits were made from freight haulage, and many lines sought to rid themselves of unprofitable passenger lines, many times to the detriment of the communities these lines served. This, in combination with the Penn Central merger and bankruptcy and the bankruptcies of other major carriers, led to the Northeast Rail Crisis and the federal government's creation of Amtrak. (See Collections 5552 and 5728 for the RLEA files on these subjects.)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (1 of 11), 1962-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1)
    ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Filings
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (2 of 11), 1962-1964 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (3 of 11), 1962-1964 (Box 164, Folder 3)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (4 of 11), 1962-1964 (Box 164, Folder 4)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (5 of 11), 1964-1967 (Box 164, Folder 5)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (6 of 11), 1964-1967 (Box 164, Folder 6)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (7 of 11), 1962-1965 (Box 164, Folder 7)
    ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Filings, research and newspaper clippings
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (8 of 11), 1962-1964 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Filings, correspondence and testimony.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (9 of 11), 1963 (Box 164, Folder 9)
    ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Filings, testimony and supporting exhibits of Leon H. Keyserling
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (10 of 11), 1962-1964 (Box 164, Folder 10)
    ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Filings, research and testimony
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad (11 of 11), 1963 (Box 164, Folder 11)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 165, Folder 1)
    Volume 41. Bound. December 10, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 165, Folder 2)
    Volume 42. Bound. December 12, 1962
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 165, Folder 3)
    Volume 43. Bound. December 14, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 165, Folder 4)
    Volume 44. Bound. December 17, 1962
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 165, Folder 5)
    Volume 45. Bound. December 19, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 165, Folder 6)
    Volume 46. Bound. December 21, 1962
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 165, Folder 7)
    Volume 47. Bound. January 9, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 165, Folder 8)
    Volume 48. Bound. January 11, 1963
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 165, Folder 9)
    Volume 49. Bound. January 14, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    Volume 54. Bound. January 21, 1963
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    Volume 55. Bound. January 22, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    Volume 56. Bound. January 28, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 4)
    Volume 62. Bound. February 15, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 5)
    Volume 63. Bound. February 18, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 6)
    Volume 63. Bound. February 19, 1963
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    Volume 65. Bound. February 20, 1963
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    Volume 66. Bound. February 21, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    Volume 74. Bound. March 27, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    Volume 75. Bound. March 28, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    Volume 76. Bound. March 29, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 12)
    Volume 77. Bound. April 1, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 13)
    Volume 78. Bound. April 2, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 14)
    Volume 107. Bound. June 13, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 15)
    Volume 108. Bound. August 6, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 16)
    Volume 109. Bound. August 7, 1963
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 17)
    Volume 110. Bound. August 8, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 18)
    Volume 123. Bound. August 27, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 166, Folder 19)
    Volume 128. Bound. October 2, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 1)
    Volume --. Bound. August 27, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 2)
    Volume 11. Bound. October 15, 1962
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 3)
    Volume 12. Bound. October 16, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 4)
    Volume 13. Bound. October 17, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 5)
    Volume 14. Bound. October 18, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 6)
    Volume 23. Bound. November 6, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 7)
    Volume 24. Bound. November 7, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 8)
    Volume 26. Bound. November 8, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 9)
    Volume 30. Bound. November 16, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 10)
    Volume 31. Bound. November 19, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 11)
    Volume 32. Bound. November 20, 1962.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 12)
    Volume 33. Bound. November 21, 1962
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 13)
    Volume 34. Bound. November 26, 1962
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1962 (Box 167, Folder 14)
    Volume 35. Bound. November 27, 1962
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 167, Folder 15)
    Volume 50. Bound. January 15, 1963
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 167, Folder 16)
    Volume 51. Bound. January 16, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 167, Folder 17)
    Volume 52. Bound. January 17, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania Railroad, ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Transcript of Proceedings, 1963 (Box 167, Folder 18)
    Volume 53. Bound. January 18, 1963.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (1 of 11), 1963-1967 (Box 168, Folder 1)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (2 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 2)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (3 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 3)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (4 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 4)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (5 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 5)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (6 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 6)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (7 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 7)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (8 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 8)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (9 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 9)
    ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21989-21990, Filings and handwritten testimony from rank-and-file members union members on the NYCRR who would lose their jobs in a merger.
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (10 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 10)
  - Mergers: New York Central and Pennsylvania (11 of 11), 1962-1963 (Box 168, Folder 11)
  - Government: ICC - Finance Dockets, 1952 (1 of 2) (Box 163, Folder 17)
    Roster of ICC Finance Docket with summaries of the cases before the committee.
  - Government: ICC - Finance Dockets, 1952 (2 of 2) (Box 163, Folder 18)
  - Transcripts of Proceedings before Referee Paul N. Guthrie regarding wage increases., 1953 (Box 169, Folder 1)
    Volume 1. Bound. January 6, 1953. In re Wage Stabilization Board. NYCRR and PRR are parties to the dispute.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings before Referee Paul N. Guthrie regarding wage increases., 1953 (Box 169, Folder 2)
    Volume 2. Bound. January 7, 1953. In re Wage Stabilization Board. NYCRR and PRR are parties to the dispute.
  - Transcripts of Proceedings before Referee Paul N. Guthrie regarding wage increases., 1953 (Box 169, Folder 3)
    Volume 3. Bound. January 8, 1953. In re Wage Stabilization Board. NYCRR and PRR are parties to the dispute.
  - Mergers: General, 1961 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - Mergers: ATSF Railroad and Western Pacific; Southern Pacific and Western Pacific, 1961 (Box 169, Folder 5)
    ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21334 and 21314
  - Mergers: Chesapeake and Ohio and Baltimore and Ohio, 1961 (Box 169, Folder 6)
    ICC Finance Docket No. 21160
  - Mergers: Great Northern Pacific and Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy, 1961 (Box 169, Folder 7)
    ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21478-21480
  - Mergers: Norfolk and Western and New York, and Chicago and St. Louis, 1961 (Box 169, Folder 8)
    ICC Finance Docket Nos. 21510, 21511, 21512, 21160, 21237
  - Mergers: Seaboard Air Line and Atlantic Coast Line, 1961 (Box 169, Folder 9)
    ICC Finance Docket No. 21215
  - Mergers: Southern Railway and Central of Georgia, 1961 (Box 169, Folder 10)
    ICC Finance Docket No. 21400
  - Mergers: Chesapeake and Ohio, Acquisition and Control of Baltimore and Ohio Railroad through Stock [folder 1 of 3], 1961-1970 (Box 170, Folder 1a)
    F.D. 21160 and 21161. Also F.D. 21237
  - Mergers: Chesapeake and Ohio, Acquisition and Control of Baltimore and Ohio Railroad through Stock [folder 2 of 3], 1961-1970 (Box 170, Folder 1b)
  - Mergers: Chesapeake and Ohio, Acquisition and Control of Baltimore and Ohio Railroad through Stock [folder 3 of 3], 1961-1970 (Box 170, Folder 1c)
  - Mergers: Chesapeake and Ohio, Acquisition and Control of Baltimore and Ohio through Stock [folder 1 of 2], 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 2a)
  - Mergers: Chesapeake and Ohio, Acquisition and Control of Baltimore and Ohio through Stock [folder 2 of 2], 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 2b)
  - Mergers: Chesapeake and Ohio, Baltimore and Ohio: Acquisition of Western Maryland Railway [folder 1 of 3], 1964-1972 (Box 170, Folder 3a)
    F.D. 23178
  - Mergers: Chesapeake and Ohio, Baltimore and Ohio: Acquisition of Western Maryland Railway [folder 2 of 3], 1964-1972 (Box 170, Folder 3b)
  - Mergers: Chesapeake and Ohio, Baltimore and Ohio: Acquisition of Western Maryland Railway [folder 3 of 3], 1964-1972 (Box 170, Folder 3c)
  - Mergers: New York Central Railroad and Alleghany Corporation Control of Baltimore and Ohio [folder 1 of 3], 1961-1963 (Box 170, Folder 4a)
    F.D. 21237. Also F.D. 21160 and 21161.
  - Mergers: New York Central Railroad and Alleghany Corporation Control of Baltimore and Ohio [folder 2 of 3], 1961-1963 (Box 170, Folder 4b)
  - Mergers: New York Central Railroad and Alleghany Corporation Control of Baltimore and Ohio [folder 3 of 3], 1961-1963 (Box 170, Folder 4c)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Abandonment, 1961 (Box 170, Folder 5)
    F.D. 21694
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad - Discussing Passenger Train, 1962-1963 (Box 170, Folder 6)
    F.D. 22094
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway Company - Abandonment, 1962-1963 (Box 170, Folder 7)
    F.D. 22356
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway - Acquisition and Abandonment [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1973 (Box 170, Folder 8a)
    Acquisition (F.D. 22449). Abandonment (F.D. 22450)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway - Acquisition and Abandonment [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1973 (Box 170, Folder 8b)
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway - Abandonment, 1963 (Box 170, Folder 9)
    F.D. 22693
  - Chesapeake and Ohio Railway - Construction and Abandonment, 1963-1964 (Box 170, Folder 10)
    F.D. 22890 (Construction). F.D. 22891 (Abandonment).
  - Chestnut Ridge Railway - Abandonment, 1961-1962 (Box 170, Folder 11)
    F.D. Number 21811
  - Chicago, Aurora and Elgin Railroad - Abandonment, 1959-1961 (Box 170, Folder 12)
    F.D. Number 20623
  - Chicago Burlington and Quincy Abandonment, 1960 (Box 170, Folder 13)
    F.D. 20967
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy - Abandonment, 1960 (Box 170, Folder 14)
    F.D. 21277
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy - Abandonment, 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 15)
    F.D. 21308
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy - Abandonment, 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 16)
    F.D. 21310
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy - Abandonment, 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 17)
    F.D. 21311
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy - Abandonment (30.44 miles, Iowa), 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 18)
    F.D. 21329
  - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy - Abandonment, 1960-1961 (Box 170, Folder 19)
    F.D. 21374
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy - Abandonment, 1961 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    F.D. 12410
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy - Abandonment, 1961 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    F.D. 21587
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad - Abandonment, 1961-1962 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    F.D. 21624
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad - Abandonment, 1961 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    F.D. 21724
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad - Abandonment, 1962 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    F.D. 21942
  - Chicago, Burlington, and Quincy Railroad - Abandonment and Construction, 1963-1967 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    F.D. 22636 (Abandonment) and F.D. 22637 (Construction)
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad - Merger, with Chicago Heights Terminal and Transfer Co., 1960-1961 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    F.D. 20915
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad - Discontinuance of Service, 1960-1961 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    F.D. 21353
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad - Investigation of Control, 1962-1967 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    F.D. 21980
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad - Abandonment, 1962-1967 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    F.D.22314
  - Chicago and Eastern Illinois Railroad - Abandonment, 1965-1966 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    F.D. 22314. Reopened - File 2.
  - Chicago Great Western Railway - Abandonment, 1961-1962 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    F.D. 21759
  - Chicago Great Western Railway - Discontinuance of Passenger Trains 5 and 6 between Kansas City and Minneapolis, 1961-1962 (Box 171, Folder 13)
    F.D. 21844
  - Chicago Great Western Railway - Abandonment, 1961-1962 (Box 171, Folder 14)
    F.D. 21850
  - Chicago Great Western Railway - Abandonment, 1963 (Box 171, Folder 15)
    F.D. 22380
  - Chicago, Kalamazoo, and Saginaw Railway and New York Central - Abandonment, 1960-1961 (Box 171, Folder 16)
    F.D. 21324
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad, Construction (1 of 4), 1940-1949 (Box 163, Folder 8)
    ICC FD 13085
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad, Construction (2 of 4), 1940-1949 (Box 163, Folder 9)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad, Construction (3 of 4), 1940-1949 (Box 163, Folder 10)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad, Construction (4 of 4), 1940-1949 (Box 163, Folder 11)
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Abandonment, 1960-1962 (Box 171, Folder 17)
    F.D. 21087
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Abandonment, 1960 (Box 171, Folder 18)
    F.D. 21198
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Discontinuance of Passenger Trains 15 and 16 between Minneapolis and Tacoma, 1960-1961 (Box 171, Folder 19)
    F.D. 21391
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad and Chicago and North Western - Trackage Rights, 1961-1967 (Box 171, Folder 20)
    F.D. 21532
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Abandonment, 1961-1962 (Box 171, Folder 21)
    F.D. 21648
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Acquisition of Milwaukee Land Company, 1961-1962 (Box 171, Folder 22)
    F.D. 21843
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Abandonment, 1962-1963 (Box 171, Folder 23)
    F.D. 22010
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Abandonment, 1962 (Box 171, Folder 24)
    F.D. 22095
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Abandonment, 1962 (Box 171, Folder 25)
    F.D. 22096
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul and Pacific Railroad - Acquisition, Construction, and Abandonment, 1962 (Box 171, Folder 26)
    F.D. 22117, 22118, and 22119
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul and Pacific Railroad - Discontinuance of Passenger Trains 15 and 16 between Aberdeen, SD and Deer Lodge, MT, 1963 (Box 171, Folder 27)
    F.D. 22428
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul and Pacific Railroad - Discontinuance of Passenger Trains 15 and 16 between Aberdeen, SD and Deer Lodge, MT, 1963- 1964 (Box 171, Folder 28)
    F.D. 22758
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Acquisition, 1963-1965 (Box 171, Folder 29)
    F.D. 22789
  - Chicago, Milwaukee, Saint Paul, and Pacific Railroad - Abandonment, 1964 (Box 171, Folder 30)
    F.D. 22953
  - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway - Abandonment [folder 1 of 2], 1958-1963 (Box 171, Folder 31a)
    F.D. 20245
  - Chicago, North Shore, and Milwaukee Railway - Abandonment [folder 2 of 2], 1958-1963 (Box 171, Folder 31b)
  - Chicago and North Western Railway - Discontinuance of Trains 510-511, 514-515 between Chicago and Duluth, 1959-1960 (Box 171, Folder 32)
    F.D. 20681